Chapter 1: After the Uproar

After knocking Takahisa off his feet and leaping down from the enchanted ship, Rio held Miharu in his arms as he landed gracefully in the rooftop garden. Satsuki and Charlotte stood in waiting.

“Haruto! Miharu! Are either of you hurt?!” As soon as Satsuki saw Rio with Miharu in his arms, she ran over in a hurry.

“No, I’m fine. Thanks to Haru-ku... Haruto,” Miharu replied, glancing up at Rio’s face. She met his eyes, then looked down in embarrassment. At the same time, Rio had a faint smile tugging at his lips, before letting Miharu down onto her feet.

“I see...” Satsuki seemed to sense the strange atmosphere as she watched Rio and Miharu’s expressions, wondering what on earth had happened. She was a little curious, but there were more important matters to address.

“What about Takahisa?”

“He’s still on the ship. Probably still knocked out,” Rio replied, looking up at the Centostella Kingdom’s enchanted ship flying far above them. The faint sense of guilt he felt was probably because he had punched Takahisa out of legitimate self-defense.

Satsuki blinked. “Knocked out... Hehe, I see,” she giggled.

“So what happens now?” Rio asked with a troubled expression.

“Now... Takahisa’s the one at fault here, since he tried to kidnap Miharu. I guess we’d have to bring him back and question him properly about why he did this. And it’ll have to be before the royals,” Satsuki said, her words laced with fury towards Takahisa. She glanced back at Charlotte, who had followed her.

“In that case, allow me to lead you three to Father,” Charlotte suggested calmly.

Satsuki looked up at the sky. “But if we don’t bring Takahisa back first, the enchanted ship might sail away from the capital like this...”

“There’s no need to worry. Sir Takahisa will be brought directly to the castle.” Charlotte spoke as though it was a settled matter.

“What?” Satsuki asked in confusion. Was it really something to be so calm about?

“The capital is currently surrounded by our kingdom’s enchanted ship fleet, so it would be extremely difficult for anyone to depart. Princess Lilianna is also with my father right now, so I cannot imagine the ship’s crew would forcibly charge through without their master on board. Doing so would even be considered a declaration of war against our kingdom,” Charlotte explained with a smile. It was almost as though she had planned for Takahisa’s rebellion in advance.

“...I see.” Satsuki gazed at her in awe. No matter how she looked at it, the preparations were too thorough.

...So an enchanted fleet has surrounded the capital, huh? Charlotte’s explanation seemed a little odd to Rio, too.

“...Why was the capital surrounded by an enchanted fleet?” Satsuki asked Charlotte.

Charlotte looked at Rio as she answered. “Sir Haruto’s efforts have greatly altered the outcome, but these were originally arrangements made to prevent Sir Takahisa’s scheme from succeeding,” she smiled impishly.

In other words, she knew that Miharu would be kidnapped, Rio guessed immediately, but wondered why she would stay silent about it.

Satsuki’s jaw dropped. “Char... Did you know that Takahisa was going to kidnap Miharu?” she asked.

“Yes,” Charlotte nodded calmly. “I was half in doubt about whether he’d actually do so, but I had received warning from Princess Lilianna of the Centostella Kingdom in advance.”

“W-Wait, hold on! Does that mean you could have stopped Takahisa’s rampage before it escalated to this?” Satsuki objected in a fluster, but Charlotte remained calm as she answered.

“I devised this as a backup plan precisely because that would be difficult. I avoided acting in advance out of fear of the worst case scenario occurring.”

Satsuki regained her composure by hearing that and sighed. “The worst case scenario?”

“A scenario where Sir Takahisa uses his divine arms to go on a rampage inside the castle before taking off with Lady Miharu on the spur of the moment, to put it simply. There would almost certainly be casualties if that were to happen, and we would lose track of both Lady Miharu and Sir Takahisa.”

“Wha...” The Takahisa she knew would never do such a thing—that was the first thought that came to Satsuki’s mind, but she quickly accepted Charlotte’s conjecture as a possibility. Takahisa had, in fact, tried to kidnap Miharu after all.

“...Yeah, I see your point. Takahisa was really backed into a corner.”

“Thank you for understanding. After the duel with Sir Haruto, Princess Lilianna learned of Sir Takahisa’s scheme and warned him against it, but he wasn’t in the right state of mind to discuss things properly. He threatened her with quitting his hero role and forcefully made her promise to assist in Lady Miharu’s kidnapping.”

Satsuki looked pained to hear that. “I see...”

“It would normally be Princess Lilianna’s duty to follow the will of her kingdom’s hero, but this time was an exception. She pretended to make various arrangements to assist Sir Takahisa while secretly making contact with Father for his support in stopping him. This all happened merely an hour ago,” Charlotte explained eloquently.

She could see he was on the verge of running amok anyway, so she wanted to let him do so in a controlled environment, huh? Rio guessed.

“And so, we had to move as secretly as possible in order to prevent the crime from happening with what little time we had. As a result, we had to overlook the risk of Lady Miharu being momentarily kidnapped, which was very regrettable. I’d like to extend my most sincere apologies, Lady Miharu.” Charlotte finished her explanation with a sorrowful apology towards Miharu.

“That’s okay, I’m here safe and sound now, thanks to Haruto.” Miharu reflexively shook her head at having a princess bow to her, but she stiffened upon making eye contact with Rio.

For some reason, it seems as though Miharu keeps getting embarrassed whenever she looks at Haruto... But Haruto seems calm about it, Satsuki observed quietly, analyzing the situation.

“We laid out the plan and watched it proceed accordingly, but the only factor that exceeded our expectations was the extent of Sir Haruto’s abilities. Seeing you retrieve Lady Miharu so easily was beyond anything we could have imagined. Honestly, it was a stunning upset.” Charlotte looked at Rio with a mischievous smile.

“It seems I went and made things worse instead. I apologize.” Rio solemnly bowed his head.

“No, no, not at all. You were able to retrieve Lady Miharu sooner that way, so it was for the best. And personally, my heart has never fluttered as much as the moment I saw you leap from the castle. You were incredible, Sir Haruto. If Father caught wind of it, I believe he’d hold you in an even higher regard,” Charlotte said, gazing at Rio with more than just inquisitive heat. She proceeded to maintain fixed eye contact with him.

Rio looked a little uncomfortable with being stared at for so long. “...I am honored.”

“Hmm...” Satsuki stared at Rio’s side profile. Miharu was also watching his face closely. When he noticed both of their gazes, Rio smoothed over his expression awkwardly.

“Hehe. Now, allow me to lead you all to Father. I’m sure there are some things to discuss before Sir Takahisa arrives as well.” Charlotte smiled alluringly and turned around to begin walking, but immediately came to a stop and spun back. “Ah, but first—there’s something I should probably tell you beforehand, as you may want to prepare yourselves before discussing this with Father present.”

“What is it?” Satsuki looked at Charlotte and asked.

“It’s the reason why I wasn’t able to inform everyone of the situation in advance. I believed it may be quite an unsettling matter to hear.” Charlotte looked a little somber as she looked from Satsuki to Miharu before finally glancing at Rio.

“What do you mean...?” Satsuki stiffened faintly, exchanging looks with Miharu.

“Lady Aki proactively cooperated in the kidnapping of Lady Miharu.”

“Wha...”

The truth that Charlotte thrust at them was more than enough to leave them shaken.

◇　◇　◇

After that, Charlotte led Rio and the others into a meeting room of the Galarc castle reserved for royalty. They had been greatly bewildered by Aki’s cooperation in Miharu’s kidnapping, but decided to prioritize relocating to the room.

Waiting inside the room was King Francois and First Princess Lilianna.

“Lady Miharu...” Lilianna blinked at the sight of Miharu. She must have been surprised to see Miharu here after Takahisa had just caused an uproar.

Meanwhile, Francois sent his daughter Charlotte a questioning look. What exactly happened? Explain the situation, his eyes said.

Charlotte giggled at their reactions. “It may seem like an unforeseen circumstance has occurred, but there’s nothing to worry about. Sir Haruto simply flew into the sky and retrieved Lady Miharu himself,” she stated succinctly. Both Francois and Lilianna were taken aback by that, their surprise showing clear on their faces.

“...Flew into the sky, you say?”

In the Strahl region, the only means of flying were to board an enchanted ship or ride a flying mount. If Rio had flown under his own power, then it was indeed something to be taken aback by.

“That’s exactly what I said. Sir Haruto used the power of his enchanted sword to leap into the sky and board the ship that Sir Takahisa was on. It seems like Sir Takahisa was knocked out onboard the ship, so it should be easy to bring him back,” Charlotte said happily, looking at Rio.

Francois had been listening in a near-daze before he determined his daughter was telling the truth, then burst into hearty laughter. “...Ha! Hahaha! I see. It’s just one surprise after another with you, Haruto,” he said, looking at Rio.

“Thank you for your kind words.” Rio bowed his head in embarrassment.

“Now, how much have you told Satsuki and the others, Charlotte?”

“I’ve already given them the general gist of how we were moving in secrecy, but it seems like they’re still a bit shocked by it all and have yet to accept the situation completely. While it’s easy to feel rage towards Sir Takahisa for directly committing the crime, there must be conflicted feelings towards Lady Aki for her secret involvement.”

“Hmm. Well, that’s understandable.” Charlotte and Francois’ gazes turned towards Satsuki and Miharu, who were beside Rio.

“Could you tell us more? I’d like to hear the details about why Takahisa and Aki decided to kidnap Miharu,” Satsuki asked, holding her breath quietly.

Francois looked at Lilianna. “It would be best for Lilianna to answer that, as she was there. But have a seat first.”

“Lady Satsuki and Lady Miharu can sit over there. Sir Haruto, please come this way.” Charlotte offered Satsuki and Miharu the empty seats of honor before softly entwining her arm around Rio’s and pulling him to sit with her.

“Excuse me.” Rio sat in the seat Charlotte offered to him. Miharu and Satsuki exchanged a meaningful look after seeing them before they took their own seats.

“Before you tell us, can I ask where Aki and Masato are right now?” Satsuki asked Francois.

“We took them into our care as soon as the commotion started. Right now we’ve left them in another room and told them that an unexpected situation has occurred.”

“Got it. Please go on, then,” Satsuki said, looking at Lilianna.

“Of course. I’ll start with Sir Takahisa’s motive behind this foolish act. As I’m sure you must know, Sir Takahisa has romantic feelings towards Lady Miharu,” Lilianna said, looking at Miharu.

“Indeed,” Satsuki nodded naturally. Meanwhile, Miharu was taken aback and looked slightly uncomfortable. Rio continued listening without any particular change in expression.

“That’s why Sir Takahisa was overjoyed to be reunited with Lady Miharu. But, at the same time, he was flustered. He panicked at the thought of a man he didn’t know getting close to Lady Miharu.”

When he heard Lilianna’s explanation, a distant look appeared in Rio’s eyes. The situations were similar: in his previous life as Amakawa Haruto, he had spotted Miharu with Takahisa after entering high school. As a result, Amakawa Haruto had felt a strong sense of loss, but an even stronger feeling of panic.

“Knowing that Lady Miharu strongly favored Sir Amakawa and knowing what kind of person Sir Amakawa is, Sir Takahisa’s panic gradually turned into a feeling of rivalry towards Sir Amakawa. Then, when Lady Miharu said she wanted to stay with Sir Amakawa, that rivalry transformed into undeniable jealousy.”

In Takahisa’s case, the panic of losing Miharu had changed into a sense of rivalry and envy instead.

“Envy can cloud a man’s judgment. This was especially so in Sir Takahisa’s case, as he tends to feel more strongly than other people. He can be immature and weak of heart, which was why he wasn’t able to view his situation objectively. He couldn’t accept reality, couldn’t face his own weakness. Unable to suppress his jealousy, he challenged Sir Amakawa to a duel, but he couldn’t give up on Lady Miharu despite his defeat... Resulting in the uproar over kidnapping Lady Miharu,” Lilianna said, giving her own analysis about Takahisa’s emotional state.

“...” Both Satsuki and Miharu fell silent with pained expressions.

“Sir Takahisa insisted that Lady Miharu would only be unhappy remaining with Sir Amakawa, so he sought a duel to pull them apart—but he actually just wanted Lady Miharu to remain by his side instead. He knew he would lose to Sir Amakawa before they even fought, but he was unwilling to accept that, and went on a childish tantrum like this instead...”

Whether it was because she had been closest to him since he arrived in this world or because she had the observing eyes of royalty, Lilianna guessed at Takahisa’s emotions accurately.

“I suppose I can understand that, if I really tried,” Satsuki said sullenly.

“Even after being defeated by Sir Amakawa, Sir Takahisa couldn’t accept the thought of being separated from Lady Miharu. Lady Aki and I followed him into the castle after he departed the arena, and it was there that he said he had thought of a plan to keep Lady Miharu away from Sir Amakawa.”

“He really is a child...” The more Satsuki listened, the greater her anger was building.

“I proposed to Sir Takahisa that we returned to our kingdom. That he should put some distance between himself and Lady Miharu, in order to cool his head. But he immediately shot me down...” Lilianna said, smiling quite sadly. “Because I had emphasized the lack of options left for Sir Takahisa, he turned to the most destructive means he had left: to forcefully bring Lady Miharu to Centostella against her will...”

Lilianna had tried to direct the conversation towards how unfeasible that would be, but unfortunately, Takahisa was past the point of reasoning by then.

Satsuki was dumbfounded. “No way... He really just thought that would work?”

“...Yes. He insisted that Lady Miharu would understand once they talked it out afterwards. It was my irresponsible words that caused all of this. Please accept my sincerest apologies.” Lilianna bowed her head, deeply regretful for her words.

“No, no one in their right mind would go ahead with that...” Satsuki defended Lilianna while feeling extremely exasperated. Miharu seemed to agree with her, as she was nodding along.

“However, the fact of the matter is that my words caused all this. I frantically tried to get Sir Takahisa to change his mind, but he wouldn’t listen to me at all. He said he would no longer return to Centostella if he couldn’t bring Lady Miharu with him, and that he would quit being a hero.”

“...” Satsuki fell speechless once again.

“If there is one thing that Princess Lilianna must prevent at all costs, it is the rebellion of the hero. For a kingdom that worships the Six Wise Gods, it would be a tragedy that could rock the land. It is a more than effective threat to make,” Francois added, joining the discussion after remaining silent up until that point.

“If Lady Satsuki rebelled against us, our kingdom would also be in a world of trouble,” Charlotte added with a giggle.

“I would never do such a thing when I’ve been given no reason to distrust our relationship,” Satsuki sighed, pressing her hand against her head.

Charlotte chose not to press the matter any further, instead turning to Lilianna with an unrelated question. “That aside, there was one thing I was wondering. Why does Sir Takahisa think that Lady Miharu would only be unhappy with Sir Haruto?”

“In the world that Lady Satsuki and Lady Miharu originally came from, the act of killing another person is extremely frowned upon. This is apparently relevant here because, well... It seems that Sir Amakawa has a history of doing so...” Lilianna explained awkwardly, looking at Rio.

“Haruto is a wandering swordsman, so it would only be natural to kill bandits and the like in self-defense on his travels. The way Princess Lilianna puts it, this act sounds like it is condemned even in the case of legitimate self-defense. Is that so, Lady Satsuki?” Francois asked curiously.

“Well... The country we came from did consider it to be socially unacceptable, even if it were for legitimate self-defense,” Satsuki answered a little bitterly.

“Our world can also deem the killing of an individual to be murder depending on the time and situation, so it appears the biggest difference is in the way they condemn what we consider acceptable by our laws and order,” Francois hummed in interest. He then steered the conversation back to Lilianna. “I apologize for interrupting. Do continue with your story, Princess Lilianna.”

“Yes, Your Majesty,” Lilianna resumed her explanation with a frown. “From the moment he started thinking of Lady Miharu’s kidnapping as a realistic option, there was no way of changing Sir Takahisa’s mind. I tried to persuade him, but to no avail, so I asked Lady Aki to assist in persuading him, but...”

“...What did Aki say to Takahisa?” Miharu asked nervously.

“She asked if it wasn’t enough for her to be there instead of Lady Miharu.”

“...And what was Takahisa’s answer?” Satsuki asked this time.

Lilianna slowly shook her head. “Nothing in words. But it was the same as answering no, as that was when Lady Aki appeared—broken—as she offered to assist Sir Takahisa...”

“I... see...” Both Satsuki and Miharu looked to be in anguish.

“There was nothing more I could do after that. Because I had strongly opposed Sir Takahisa’s plans, he seemed to be a little wary of me, which caused tension between us...” Lilianna said vaguely, frowning.

“So you ended up cooperating with Takahisa?” Satsuki guessed.

“Yes. But only on the surface. At that point, I had given up on resolving this alone. I conceded my allegiance to Sir Takahisa then went behind his back to seek assistance from King Francois in resolving the situation.” She probably hadn’t wanted to betray Takahisa like this, as Lilianna’s expression showed glimpses of guilt.

“Lady Miharu, Lady Satsuki, and Haruto. I apologize for not being able to inform you of the situation in advance.” A king should never lower his head so easily, but at that moment, Francois bowed his head in a solemn apology.

“No, if anything, it’s my responsibility that things turned out like this... I’m very sorry for all the trouble I’ve caused everyone.” Miharu bowed her head in return, regretful of her own lack of action in confronting Aki. If only she hadn’t feared their relationship turning sour, if only she hadn’t passively remained beside Aki while ignoring the issue she had carried for many years...

At that, Satsuki spoke up with a conflicted expression. “I also believe this was the best way for things to be handled, so if Miharu accepts it, then I have nothing more to add,” she said. While she had some objections to how the countermeasures that were planned had turned a blind eye to Miharu’s momentary kidnapping, she didn’t think she would have come up with a better solution if she were in Francois’ position. Speaking up would only worsen the situation into what Francois and Charlotte had feared.

“As long as the two of them are in agreement, I have no objections, either,” Rio added, the final one of them to speak.

“I see... That only leaves the matter of how to deal with Sir Takahisa and Lady Aki, then. On behalf of our kingdom, I would like to respect Lady Satsuki and Lady Miharu’s opinions first and foremost...” Francois finally touched upon the topic of how to deal with Takahisa and Aki and looked towards Satsuki and Miharu as the two people who came from the same hometown as the culprits.

“Even if you ask us, Takahisa’s still a hero of the Centostella Kingdom, so there’s no way for us to give an opinion without hearing Princess Lilianna’s thoughts first...” Satsuki replied, passing the question on to Lilianna.

“My kingdom will not treat Sir Takahisa as a criminal, but I do intend on enforcing some kind of punishment. I would like to come to an agreement on what that penalty involves,” Lilianna said firmly.

“What kind of penalty were you thinking of?” Satsuki asked.

“When I offered to cooperate in Lady Miharu’s kidnapping, I made Sir Takahisa sign a contract with me. He agreed to accept whatever punishment I decide on if he were to fail at the kidnapping attempt. There were several items detailed which I shall show you later, but if you have any requests then I am prepared to apply that penalty on Sir Takahisa,” Lilianna said fluently.

“I see... I don’t think we’d be able to say anything for certain without seeing that contract, but...” Satsuki turned to Miharu. “What do you think?”

Miharu’s face twisted in pain. “I... Instead of a punishment—and I don’t know if the current Takahisa will be capable of doing this—I’d like the two of them to think carefully about what they did wrong and apologize to everyone they’ve hurt, including Haruto.”

Lilianna watched Miharu closely before opening her mouth with a slightly downcast look in her eyes. “Of course, if he sincerely wants to apologize, then that would be for the best, but as Lady Miharu said, it may not be possible for him to do that, with the way he is now. I believe the best penalty would be to show him that a simple apology won’t be enough to gain forgiveness. I don’t intend to forgive him so easily for this incident, either.” She wouldn’t just sweep it under the rug. There was a quiet fury to Lilianna’s words as she implied that.

“Indeed, it wouldn’t benefit him to be forgiven so easily. I completely agree. What do you think, Haruto?” Satsuki asked.

“I... am worried about how Aki will be treated for cooperating with Takahisa,” Rio said.

“I am prepared to bring her to my kingdom as originally planned, if she still wishes to do so. But I don’t have any particular punishment in mind, so if Lady Miharu and Lady Satsuki have any requests, then I shall arrange to fulfill them.” Just like with Takahisa’s case, Lilianna sought Miharu and Satsuki’s opinions for how to handle Aki.

“I don’t believe Aki should be forgiven so easily, either. I’m sure Miharu will want to forgive Aki as soon as she sees her in pain, but that would be the biggest punishment and best for her own sake. That’s why I think it would be better for Miharu and Haruto to avoid seeing her for a while. What do you think?” After giving her opinion on the matter, Satsuki looked at Miharu first.

Miharu pondered the reason why Aki would want to cooperate with Takahisa and found her own feelings wanting to remain by Aki’s side, so she forced those feelings down and nodded. “That’s... Yeah. That may be for the best.”

It wouldn’t help Aki if Miharu continued to interact with her as she had until now. It would only cause the same thing to happen again.

“What about you, Haruto?” Satsuki inquired.

Rio had hesitated for a moment, but soon nodded. “...I have no objections. Does that mean that even if Aki states she wants to follow Miharu instead, she’d be made to stay with Takahisa? Is that correct?”

“If that happens, I’ll watch over Aki instead, in which case I’ll have to ask for the Galarc Kingdom’s cooperation to allow her to stay here. Is that all right, King Francois?” Satsuki asked.

“Of course. We were prepared to welcome your friends from the beginning,” Francois nodded easily.

“Thank you very much,” Satsuki bowed her head. Miharu followed her lead. Just then, someone knocked on the door of the meeting room.

“Who is it?” Francois replied, but Charlotte stood up from her seat. They had ordered everyone else to leave, so there was no one else available to answer the door. Considering their positions, Rio couldn’t let a princess superior to him handle the errands, so he also stood up to accompany her.

“I’ll get the door.”

“Oh my, it’s like I’ve gained my own personal guard. How delightful.” Rio took the lead and opened the door, to Charlotte’s joy. On the other side of the door stood a knight different to the ones standing on guard.

“The hero of the Centostella Kingdom has been brought to the castle. Shall I escort him here?” he reported, placing his right hand over his chest in a show of respect.

“How is he acting? Any signs of struggling?” Francois asked from where he was seated.

“None, Your Majesty. He does seem a little sullen, but is maintaining his silence.”

“I see. In that case, let him wait in the room next door.”

“Yes, Your Majesty.” The knight bowed his head respectfully before departing. Rio quietly closed the door behind him.

“Now, let us return, Sir Haruto.” Charlotte pressed up close against Rio as they returned to their seats.

“What would you like to do? I have no reason to meet with Sir Takahisa before anyone else here,” Francois asked, looking at Satsuki and Lilianna.

“I’d like to talk to Takahisa and Aki alone for a bit. On behalf of Miharu and Haruto, that is,” Satsuki requested.

“In that case, Lady Aki shall be brought to the next room, too. Princess Lilianna, if you have anything to discuss with Sir Takahisa, you may head next door first,” said Francois.

“No, it would be easier for me to speak with both Sir Takahisa and Lady Aki present, so I shall wait for Lady Aki to arrive. I can do so after Lady Satsuki speaks with them first,” Lilianna decided.

“In that case, would you like to sit in, too, Princess Lilianna? We can discuss everything at once that way,” Satsuki asked, extending a request for Lilianna to join her.

“I understand. Let’s go with that, then.” Lilianna nodded solemnly.

“Thank you. Miharu and Haruto, could you go call Masato and explain things to him, then?” With Satsuki handling Takahisa and Aki, she entrusted Masato to Miharu and Rio.

“...Yes, leave it to us.” A shadow fell over Miharu’s face as she nodded hesitantly. She had realized that now was not the time to meet the two of them.

“Then I shall send a summons for Lady Aki and Sir Masato. Lady Aki will be led to the meeting room next door, and Sir Masato will be brought to this room,” said Francois.

◇　◇　◇

Aki and Masato’s arrival was announced ten minutes later. Satsuki and Lilianna headed out while Masato took their place in the room with Rio and Miharu.

“Haruto, Miharu—what on earth happened? Aki looked like a ghost the entire time before they led her to another room.” Masato had bumped into Satsuki while they were swapping rooms and was told to ask Rio and Miharu for the details, leaving him confused from the moment he entered the room.

“We’ll explain everything. Have a seat first,” Rio said to Masato as calmly as possible.

Francois, who was still present in the meeting room, stood up. “Hmm. Then Charlotte and I shall leave this to you, Haruto.”

“Thank you for your consideration, Your Majesty.”

Rio immediately stood up and bowed his head at Francois, his right hand over his heart. Miharu hurried to stand up and bow her head with Rio.

“It’s fine. I shall have Charlotte tell me of your heroic feats earlier. Let’s go.” Francois smiled happily and left the room with Charlotte, leaving Rio, Miharu, and Masato alone in the room.

“How about you have a seat over here, Masato?” Miharu suggested Masato take the seat she had been in and moved to sit beside Rio.

“Sure...” Masato sat down across from Rio and Miharu, watching their expressions carefully.

“So, umm. This may come as a surprise to you, but...” Miharu began hesitantly.

“Miharu, I can do the explaining,” Rio offered. He thought it cruel for Miharu to have to speak about it, as she was the victim in the situation.

“W-What is it...?” Masato could feel the unusual mood in the air and stiffened cautiously.

“I’m sure it’ll be a shock to hear this, so I’ll say it as simply as possible. Takahisa made an unsuccessful attempt to kidnap Miharu. Aki cooperated with him,” Rio said curtly.

“...Wha?”

Sure enough, Masato froze in shock.

“Takahisa and Aki summoned us to that garden under the guise of saying farewell, when they actually intended to kidnap Miharu. After everyone split up and Miharu was left with Takahisa, he abducted her. Now, Satsuki and Princess Lilianna are talking to the two of them next door.”

“...Are you serious?” Masato muttered in a daze.

“Yes, I’m serious. Some people in the castle spotted them and made a commotion, and Princess Lilianna herself testified as soon as she learned of their plans. Not to mention I was the one who retrieved Miharu from the enchanted ship,” Rio said, listing the facts in a stiff voice.

“Argh... Damn it, what are those two doing...” Masato muttered, his face scrunched up on the verge of tears.

“Masato...” Miharu bit down on her lip.

“Sorry, Miharu. For my brother and sister...” Masato apologized to Miharu as though it was his own mistake.

“Don’t apologize, Masato. I was at fault, too. Even though I was the closest one to Aki, I continuously ignored the problem she carried in her heart...” Miharu said with an agonized expression, feeling guilt in her heart.

“While I can’t say for sure that your thoughts are wrong, don’t you think they’re a little off the mark? The ones who should bear the burden of the crime are the criminals alone. Even bearing a part of the burden for someone who committed a crime won’t be of benefit to them. That’s why it’s not either of your faults. Of course, I have no intention of denying how important the two of them are to you, but if you don’t detach yourselves, you’ll just be contributing to a vicious cycle,” Rio said logically.

“But... What should I do, then...?” Masato whispered, his voice barely audible. Rio’s words seemed to have reached his heart, but he still felt clueless.

“What matters is what you want to do, not what you should do. Think about what you want to do, then reverse calculate what you can do about it. Reality may not work out that smoothly, as you may have many things you want to do and some of them may contradict with each other... Why don’t you give it some thought? Take some time to come to grips with the truth first, then think about it.” A faint shadow was cast over Rio’s face as he advised Masato in a gentle voice.

“Haruto...” Masato murmured. He was deeply touched.

“At the very least, I don’t think any of the blame should fall on you, Masato. The same goes for Miharu. You don’t believe Miharu’s at fault, either. Right, Masato?”

“Y-Yeah! Of course not!”

“In that case, stop blaming yourself. You can start there.”

“All right...” Masato nodded his head obediently.

“You, too.” Rio looked at Miharu beside him.

“O-Okay.” Miharu was so absorbed in Rio’s words, she flinched when she was suddenly addressed.

“Please don’t take on more responsibility than you need to. If you really treasure the two of them, instead of bearing the weight of their crimes, become their support, even if that means you need to be harsh and push them away. That’s why it would be better to stay away from them for a while, don’t you think?”

“...Yes, that’s right.”

“So please stop blaming yourself. That’s all I wanted to say,” Rio said in conclusion, shrugging his shoulders with a sigh.

Chapter 2: Masato’s Decision

“I have something to say,” Masato said quietly.

“...Right, okay. Come in, Masato.” Miharu could tell Masato had something important to say from the look on his face and invited him inside with a gentle tone. Masato nodded before following Miharu into the room.

“Come—sit down.”

“Okay.”

Satsuki had encouraged Masato to take the seat next to hers. Miharu returned to her original place beside Rio so that the four of them were seated facing each other in pairs.

“You want to talk about Takahisa and Aki, right?” Satsuki asked, looking at Masato.

“Yeah. Neither of them were in a state to hold a conversation, so I just sent them to their rooms with Princess Lilianna and came back...”

“Did something happen?”

“No, nothing in particular happened, but...” Masato looked down and frowned in frustration. He paused before lifting his head. “The two of them will be taken to the Centostella Kingdom soon, right?” he asked nervously.

“Yes, most likely. Takahisa is the hero of Centostella, so Princess Lilianna has no choice but to take him back to her kingdom, otherwise she’d be in trouble. If Aki chooses to stay... I can ask the king if she can live with me in this castle for a while,” Satsuki said.

“I see... That’s right...” A shadow fell over Masato’s face.

Satsuki exchanged glances with Rio and Miharu. “Would you prefer if they didn’t go to Centostella?”

“No, that wouldn’t be right. They may have done something incredibly stupid, but even that stupid brother of mine is needed by the Centostella Kingdom—I know this well, because Haruto’s said it many times now. I agree with the three of you... I can’t forgive them so easily, either. If they remain around Miharu and Haruto without even reflecting on their actions, I’m worried they’ll try something again in the future. That’s why I know it’s best to keep them distant. But still, even then...” Masato trailed off, wondering if it was right to say what he was about to say. He seemed at a terrible loss for words.

“Don’t hold back—just say what you’re thinking. No one will dismiss you without listening first,” Rio urged.

“...Even then, those two stupid siblings are my siblings. Seeing Aki sobbing and Takahisa sulking when it was all his fault to begin with made me feel really pathetic as their brother. I can’t just sit still and watch Princess Lilianna take care of the two of them. Why should someone else have to clean up after my fallen family? Honestly, I don’t want to stay with them, but I feel like I have to.” Masato spat out the mixed feelings he had swirling in his chest and clenched his teeth.

“Masato...” Miharu and Satsuki were both speechless, their faces gloomy.

“...I see. So what do you want to do, Masato?” Rio asked calmly so that he wouldn’t frighten him.

“I want to follow the two of them to Centostella and help them get their lives back on track, I think. I do have doubts as to whether making such a sudden change of mind would benefit them or not, so I don’t know if this is the right decision, but...”

He had gone as far as arguing with his brother to follow his original decision of staying with Rio, but now he was making the complete opposite choice. Masato was terribly anxious about choosing which path he needed to go down.

“Those two are connected to everyone here in a similar but vastly different way. Our situations are completely different. It’s obvious that decisions will vary on an individual level, and what is right or not will vary too—if anything, it’s more common to be unsure of what’s right. There’s no guarantee that what you want to do will be what’s right. Honestly, you should just value your own will and do what you won’t regret later. As long as you don’t tread down a clearly dangerous path, we’ll support your decision. If you want us to give you our opinion, just say the word,” Rio said, advising Masato as his elder.

“Then can you tell me what you guys think about this...?” Masato asked with an imploring look.

“I don’t think either option is wrong. You’re the only one here who is both their family and an outsider to the incident. It isn’t unnatural for you to feel like you should do something about this, and you won’t be a bad influence just by being near them, unlike Miharu and I,” said Rio.

His point was about how Miharu was certainly a sister-like presence to Aki, but she had been the victim of this incident and a huge part of the motive behind the crime. It was easy to reach the conclusion that she shouldn’t be near her.

“I’m in general agreement with Haruto. However, Takahisa won’t be able to look after you and Aki the way he is right now, so you should consider yourself as well. I can’t leave the Galarc Kingdom and you won’t have Haruto or Miharu with you. You’ll have to be more responsible for yourself than ever before.” Satsuki agreed with Rio, but worried for Masato.

Masato nodded. “Yeah, I know that.”

“...” Meanwhile, Miharu had her mouth shut as she watched on with a worried look.

“Are you wondering if it’d be better for you to go, too, Miharu?” Satsuki asked.

“...No, I still feel like I need to stay away from the two of them.” Miharu shook her head slowly. Her heart felt heavy whenever she thought of Aki, but doing what Aki wanted would just be spoiling her again. Doing nothing was the best thing Miharu could do for Aki right now.

“I see...” Satsuki looked troubled, but, at the same time, a little pleased.

“Well, there’s no need for you to have an answer right now. You can use all of the remaining time until those two depart for Centostella. You haven’t told Princess Lilianna yet, either, right?” Rio said to Masato to help him relax.

“Yeah. I was still conflicted about this after I escorted them to their rooms... But I feel a little better after talking to you guys. Thanks.” Masato chuckled like his usual self.

“Hehe, I’m relieved to see you smile like that. It’s a tough time for all of us, but that’s why we have to stay positive. Being gloomy will only make you feel gloomy too,” Satsuki said with a gentle smile.

“Yeah. If anything, I’d like to show Takahisa and Aki that we’re all able to laugh happily. That would have a greater effect on those two.” Masato snickered wickedly.

“Hehe.” Miharu and Rio both chuckled.

“That aside, Haruto—I have a separate request to make...” Masato suddenly said.

“What is it?”

“Could you bring me to the stone house tonight? The others might leave from the kingdom as early as tomorrow, and I’d like to see everyone before then. This could be goodbye for now, and I want to tell them about Aki, as well...”

He worded it as a possibility, but Masato had probably made his decision already. His grinning face looked a tiny bit sorrowful.

Rio pretended he didn’t see it and nodded with a slightly troubled look. “...Yeah, sure.”

Miharu and Satsuki both seemed to notice as well, but chose to watch their conversation instead of speaking up.

“Ah, I don’t like depressing moods. After we’re done talking to everyone, let’s take a bath together. I’ll wash your back for you,” Masato said to Rio to clear the heavy atmosphere hanging over them.

“Sure, let’s do it.”

“Yeah,” Masato replied happily.

“Hmm, a bath. That sounds nice... Right, Miharu?” Satsuki joined in the conversation with a playfully interested tone, as though she was responding to Masato’s request for a less depressing mood.

“Yes. I’d like one, too,” Miharu nodded with a giggle.

Rio thought for a moment. “...Then shall we all head to the stone house?” he suggested.

“Huh? But shouldn’t I stay here on guard...?” She had said it pretty much half-jokingly, so Satsuki was a little shocked that permission was given so easily.

“The security around the castle hasn’t eased after the attack on the banquet, but there’s nothing we can do about that. We need this for a refresher, like Masato said. Instead, we can come back a little earlier. Of course, if you’re still worried, you can stay back...” Rio said, giving Satsuki the option to choose.

“Guh... I’m going!”

Satsuki was conflicted for a moment before losing to the temptations of the bath in the stone house. Unable to pass up the opportunity, it was decided that the four of them would head to the stone house that night.

◇　◇　◇

That night, after everyone would have fallen asleep, Rio and the others departed from Satsuki’s balcony in the pitch-black darkness to head to the stone house.

They moved with the usual help from Aishia, Rio carrying Satsuki in a bridal carry with Masato on his back while Aishia carried Miharu. They left the capital and arrived at the stone house in no time at all. Aishia had warned everyone in advance, so Celia, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma were all waiting outside.

“Welcome back!” Latifa took the lead in energetically welcoming their return. When she noticed Masato was there and Aki wasn’t, she made a slightly confused face.

“And welcome, Satsuki,” Latifa said to Satsuki in a friendly tone.

“Hi, Latifa—I’ll be intruding for a short while. Good evening, everyone,” Satsuki returned their greetings with a graceful smile.

“Good evening,” Celia and the others replied warmly. “There’s no point in standing around, so let’s go inside.”

Once they arrived in the living room...

“There are several things we’d like to tell everyone today, and it has to do with why Aki isn’t here. Shall we have a seat first?” Rio began, encouraging them to sit down.

Aishia had informed them that Rio and the others were coming, but hadn’t mentioned why, so Celia and the others stiffened slightly and exchanged glances before sitting down on the sofa in a row. Across from them sat Rio, Miharu, Satsuki, Masato, and Aishia, so it was like they were sitting face to face.

“To start with the conclusion, Aki will be going with Takahisa to the kingdom of Centostella. Or, well, that’s what most likely will end up happening at present. If she says she wants to stay, then there’s the chance that she can remain at the Galarc castle, but...” Rio trailed off.

“You’re being strangely evasive. Did something happen?” Celia asked softly, watching Rio’s face.

“Masato wants to explain that, being their younger brother.” Rio handed things over to Masato.

“Umm, thanks to Haruto and everyone here, those of us who came here from Earth were able to safely reunite with each other, but... Though we were reunited, we still ended up arguing about who would go where. Between Miharu, Aki, and myself... As well as my brother...” Masato was a little nervous, as he began his explanation with difficulty. “We all discussed it at the castle. The biggest factor was that Satsuki and my brother are heroes, so they can’t leave their respective kingdoms. In a situation like that, Miharu and I wanted to stay with Haruto, but my brother wanted us to go with him... Aki wanted to stay with him, so she obeyed...”

Celia and the others listened to Masato speak in silence. They knew that Aki had a strong attachment to her brother, as they had witnessed it first-hand, and they also knew she adored Miharu just as much—if not more. That was why they weren’t too surprised to hear there had been arguments about who was going where, however...

“To put it bluntly, my brother was in love with Miharu. But Miharu didn’t share the sentiment, since her feelings are for Haruto, so he got really jealous. It was so obvious, even a bystander could see it.”

Masato’s unexpected information made Celia and the others startle in shock. Every one of them turned to stare at Miharu. As soon as she processed Masato’s words, she turned bright red.

“...W-Wait, what are you saying, Masato?!”

“Huh...?” Masato made a perplexed face for a moment, before soon correcting his mistake. “Ah, I was talking about how my brother was jealous of Haruto, which is the reason why he caused such a commotion...”

He seemed to realize what was wrong with his statement about Miharu’s feelings for Rio. His head had been occupied with the explanation of the situation, so it was a completely accidental slip of the tongue. “H-Huh? Was I wrong?” He tried to offer a way out, but it was too late to cover up the obvious.

“A-About what?” Miharu’s eyes wandered as she tried to play dumb. Rio was maintaining an uncomfortable silence after being mixed up in the situation.

“Hrrmmm...” Latifa was glaring at Rio.

Meanwhile, Sara, Orphia, and Alma were exchanging meaningful looks. Incidentally, Celia had completely frozen with her eyes the size of saucers.

What a sinful man you are, Haruto...

Satsuki saw the reaction of the women of the stone house and sighed tiredly. She stared at Rio with a disapproving pout on her lips.

“A-Anyway, let me continue.” Masato regretted his ill-timed words and forcefully changed the subject.

“Th... That’s...” Miharu mumbled quietly, shocked. It was a series of verbal slips on Masato’s part.

“A-At any rate, my brother went on a jealousy-fueled rampage. He challenged Haruto to a petty duel over Miharu and got beaten up, but...” Masato hurried with his continuation, rattling on until he reached a good place to pause.

The nuance is slightly off if you say we were dueling over Miharu, though, Rio thought dubiously. He had actually fought to stop Takahisa from restraining Miharu’s ability to choose what she wanted to do, but the way Masato said it made it sound like a classic plot of the winner receiving Miharu’s hand in marriage...

But, whether that doubt was right or not, Celia and the others twitched in reaction to Rio’s duel over Miharu.

“For whatever unthinkable reason, after losing the duel my brother decided to kidnap Miharu and take her to the Centostella Kingdom by force.”

“Huh?!” Everyone immediately stiffened at the news that Miharu was kidnapped.

“Are you okay, Miharu?!” Sara asked in a panic.

Miharu smiled gently to reassure everyone. “Yeah. Haruto saved me right away. I wasn’t even harmed—everything’s all right.”

“Thank goodness...” Celia, Sara, Orphia, Alma, and Latifa all sighed in relief.

“But I think Aki has it worse than me, so...” Miharu looked at Masato with a frown, encouraging him to continue.

“Like Miharu said, the problem is Aki. I know it’ll be a shock to hear, but Aki assisted my brother in the attempt to kidnap Miharu,” Masato said with a stiff expression.

“Wha...” Everyone was rendered speechless; the first one to speak up was Celia.

“...What is Aki doing now?”

“She’s in the castle with my brother.”

“A kidnapping incident within the castle walls is normally enough to warrant an execution. Were they punished in any way...?”

“That won’t happen... I think. Right, Haruto?” Hearing the word “execution” made Masato slightly nervous.

“The punishment is limited to being placed under supervision as she’s the little sister of the hero. Similarly, as long as Satsuki and Miharu don’t seek a more severe punishment, the Galarc Kingdom’s king has decided not to pursue an aggressive form of punishment against Takahisa. And the Centostella Kingdom won’t act against their own hero, either,” Rio answered, reassuring everyone.

“I see... So what are you guys going to do about Aki?” Celia asked.

“No matter the motive, the fact is that she tried to kidnap Miharu. It isn’t something that should be forgiven easily, and doing so won’t benefit Aki. That’s why we discussed things and agreed that the victim shouldn’t be the one to reach out without some kind of action from Aki first,” Rio answered stiffly.

Celia frowned, her expression pained. “I see...”

“Of course, there’s a lot that we want to say to them. But Aki’s been too dependent on Miharu, so we decided that we had to harden our hearts a bit here. We have to make her think about what she did wrong and apologize by herself.” Satsuki pursed her lips as though she had swallowed something bitter. If Miharu forgave Aki here, it was likely that Aki would cling onto Miharu’s sense of kindness...

　“...While I haven’t known her as long as Miharu has, I know that Aki isn’t a hopelessly terrible child. That’s why I’m sure she must be reflecting on things right now. She should be wanting to apologize. When she does, I hope you’ll scold her a lot, talk a lot, and make up,” Sara said, vexed and frustrated.

“We all feel the same way, Sara,” Orphia said with a gentle smile.

“Right. Her ill feelings towards Haruto have worsened a lot over the years, so it’ll be difficult for her to come forward with honesty, but if she can come to terms with those feelings and apologize sincerely to Miharu and Haruto, I think we’d all be able to go back to normal. If that’s what Aki wants,” Satsuki said with a gentle expression.

Masato closed his eyes in thought. “...Well, when I went to see her, she was sobbing so hard she couldn’t even speak, so I bet she’s reflecting on it. But my brother’s even worse than Aki in many ways, so I think it’d be bad if those two remained together alone,” he said wearily.

“...That may be true,” Satsuki agreed with difficulty.

Masato’s face twisted bitterly. “But I don’t think that means my brother should be left alone, either. He’d sulk and become stubborn, so that won’t be good. If you force Aki away from him, she might rebel, as well. That would just create more trouble. Honestly, I feel bad for having siblings that are such pains in the ass...” He bowed his head at all of them.

“There’s no need to apologize,” Rio said, the others echoing him in agreement.

“Since Aki says she wants to stay of her own accord, there’s a high chance the two of them will remain together... I think it’d be better to have someone to be there with them, telling them off so they don’t end up straying from the correct path. It has to be someone who can stand up to my siblings without backing down. So that means... that means...” Masato paused for a long moment, as though to confirm his feelings. Then, he said resolutely: “That means the only one possible is me, their brother.

“It can’t be Miharu, who’s loved by the two of them. Or Satsuki, who’s admired by the two of them. Or Haruto, who’s envied and resented by them. It has to be someone who can argue with them on a familial level, as a sibling. No one else would work. I can’t really put the reason into words, but I feel like I have to be the one to do this. That’s why...”

He couldn’t explain the reason well, but everyone present understood what was in heart. As proof of that, they were all listening to Masato’s words seriously and gazing upon him with respect.

“That’s why I talked to Haruto and the others and thought about this a lot. I’m going to go. If I have to let those two go to the Centostella Kingdom like this, then I’ll go with them. I wanted to tell you all this, so I asked to be in charge of the explanation of the incident to you all. That’s how it is, so...” Masato trailed off, unable to find the right words to explain the reasoning of his thoughts. He appeared a little uneasy.

“Are you still doubting your decision?” Rio asked Masato.

“That’s not it, I don’t think. It’s just... I can’t help but wonder what everyone thinks about this...” Masato said, looking at everyone’s faces. He was still only twelve years old—it was understandable for him to be uneasy.

“I think you’re amazing,” Rio said immediately.

“...Huh?”

“I think you’re amazing, Masato. I’m the kind of person to hesitate and distance myself, so I admire that earnest positivity of yours. I respect it. It’s almost dazzling to see...” Rio said, commending Masato from the bottom of his heart. Aki was Amakawa Haruto’s little sister, but he hadn’t been able to do anything brother-like. Even after reuniting in this world, he had been unable to grasp the sense of distance between them and ignored the issue like Miharu had done.

“I think you’re amazing, too,” Satsuki said. “As their friend and upperclassman, I want to do something about those two... But there’s a line I shouldn’t cross. I don’t know where that line is, so I believe the best choice for me right now is to keep my distance and refrain from forgiving them easily. I realized there are things we can’t do for them even if we stay with them. I didn’t have the courage to go that far, I didn’t consider things enough. But, Masato, you’re able to do all that. That’s why you’re amazing.”

“I agree. Masato looks radiant for being able to do what we can’t. I... Aki adored me as an older sister, but I always held back when it came to mentioning Haruto before her. I couldn’t be her older sister in the true sense. Masato, even though you met Aki after me, you’ve become her family more than me. I feel so disappointed in myself... That’s why you look dazzling, Masato,” Miharu said, looking at Masato admiringly.

“You’re already a wonderful adult, Masato,” Sara giggled.

“I know, right?”

“Yep.”

Orphia and Alma both nodded their agreement.

“It’s true. You’ve become stronger and more admirable than me, the eldest one here.” Celia also saw Masato as someone radiant, though she had a faint shadow over her face.

“Masato is an adult,” Aishia uttered.

“Hehe, you’re so cool, Masato,” Latifa praised with a carefree smile.

“W-What are you all going on about? Gosh...” The continuous praise and illuminated gazes of everyone made Masato blush in embarrassment.

“If it’s you, Masato, we can leave it to you and not worry about it. That’s what it means,” Satsuki giggled, winking mischievously.

“I-In that case, you can all rest assured and leave everything to me! I don’t want this incident to be the reason for everyone to be gloomy. Just sit back and live like you always have. T-That’s right—Haruto, let’s go take that bath. I’ve been looking forward to that. Let’s go, yeah? I’ll wash your back for you!”

Unable to bear the embarrassment any longer, Masato started rambling rapidly. He stood up and pulled Rio by the hand, briskly rushing away to the bathroom.

Chapter 3: Farewell, Onto a New Journey

The morning after Masato informed the residents of the stone house of his decision to go to Centostella, he was accompanied by Rio and the others to go and discuss things with Lilianna. There, he explained his thoughts and asked for Lilianna’s permission to go to Centostella to help Takahisa and Aki turn over a new leaf.

Lilianna didn’t have any confidence in her own ability to assist Takahisa and Aki right now, so she welcomed Masato with a deep bow of her head. It was decided that Masato would move from Satsuki’s quarters to Lilianna’s from that night onwards.

They would depart from the Galarc Kingdom in two days’ time, and in that time he would visit Satsuki’s quarters often to report on Takahisa and Aki’s status. Apparently, they had gotten into a huge fight right off the bat, and were currently giving each other the cold shoulder.

Then, the day of their departure finally came. In the central garden of the Galarc castle, Masato and Lilianna exchanged farewells with Rio, Miharu, and Satsuki.

“Later, then. I’ll be going now.”

“Take care, Masato.”

“You too, Miharu,” Masato grinned brightly.

“Don’t push yourself too hard, and stay out of trouble. I know you’re a picky eater, so make sure you eat balanced meals, okay?” Miharu was worrying so much like a mother, Masato could only nod with a strained smile.

“Yeah, I know.”

“Aki and Takahisa, too... Take care of them.”

“Of course. Leave the two of them to me. I’m in the middle of a huge fight with Takahisa, but I’ll fight with him as much as I need to. Rather than worrying about me, you should focus on supporting Haruto the best you can, Miharu,” Masato said, looking at Rio.

“I won’t do anything that would inconvenience Miharu,” Rio chuckled.

“That’s not what I meant...” Masato glanced at Miharu and decided not to say anything that would anger her, changing the topic smoothly instead. “Oh well. Take care, Haruto. I’ll continue practicing my sword over there, as well, so I’ll show you my growth next time.”

“...Yeah.” Rio seemed to sense what Masato was hinting at, as he nodded rather awkwardly.

“You take care, too, Satsuki,” Masato said.

“I will. I’ll always be in the castle, so you have to send me letters regularly, okay? If I don’t receive any letters I’ll assume something happened and march over there,” Satsuki said jokingly.

“Ahaha, got it,” Masato agreed lightly. Beside him stood Lilianna, who smiled.

“While letters are important, I can promise to bring Sir Masato to the Galarc Kingdom on a regular basis. Our kingdom is closed off, but I am much indebted to everyone and vow to do my best. I understand if you do not wish to visit, but if you do, I will welcome you,” she said with a respectful bow.

“That isn’t the case at all. Please show us around Centostella one day.”

“Gladly,” Satsuki giggled, making Lilianna smile in return.

Masato rubbed his nose shyly. “...Shall we get going, then? Talking any longer will just make me feel sad,” he suggested to Lilianna.

“Sure, if that is what you wish,” Lilianna nodded warmly.

“Hehe. See you all, then. I really don’t like depressing moods, so let’s part with a smile, yeah?” Masato said with a mischievous smile.

“I’ll write you lots of letters, too. Feel free to write to me if you’re ever worried about anything,” Satsuki said to Masato’s back as he departed.

“I will, thanks!” Masato turned back and thanked her before leaving with a wave. Lilianna followed from diagonally behind him, and her attendant Frill silently followed at a distance.

“There he goes. Gosh, did you see him show off? Since when did he act so similarly to a certain someone, I wonder,” Satsuki said, glancing at Rio’s side profile.

“Do you mean... Takahisa?” That was the only name that came to Rio’s mind, but—

“Nope, not that,” Satsuki denied.

“Hehe.” Miharu seemed to have an idea who that someone was, as she was giggling in amusement.

“Well, it seems like that someone is completely oblivious, so if anything, he’s more like a copycat, I guess,” Satsuki sighed.

“...?” Rio simply cocked his head in confusion.

◇　◇　◇

After Masato parted with Rio and the others, he walked forward without stopping. Knowing he would feel reluctant to leave if he turned back, he chose to walk forward in silence. Lilianna followed diagonally behind him in silence, as well.

“You’re very strong, Sir Masato,” she said to him warmly.

“...I am?” Masato slowed down and cocked his head in wonder.

“From what I can see, yes.”

“How so?”

“I believe the ability to act for someone else’s sake without expecting anything in return is the embodiment of a strong mind. Most people would normally think so highly of themselves, they would never make a sacrifice for another person’s well-being. Even if that person was their own family,” Lilianna said, frowning slightly.

“...Haha.” Masato looked shy for a moment. “If you’re going to say that, then Haruto’s much stronger than me. He did all sorts of things to help us out without anything in return.”

“Indeed, Sir Amakawa is a very wonderful person,” Lilianna nodded with a soft smile.

“...Do you like men like Haruto, Princess Lilianna? Have you fallen for Haruto?” Masato asked curiously. As far as Masato knew, all the women around Rio had fallen for him without exception. That was why he wondered how Rio appeared to Lilianna, since she only became acquainted recently and was less familiar with him.

Lilianna blinked in wonder. “Goodness, no. I am not familiar enough with Sir Amakawa to feel any such adoration for him. Even if I did, Sir Amakawa already has so many lovely ladies surrounding him—there would be no place for me.” She shook her head with a hearty laugh.

“No, no, Miharu and Satsuki are beautiful, but Princess Lilianna is just as beautiful in my eyes...” Masato said in exasperation to Lilianna’s self-depreciation of her own beauty.

“Well, I’m grateful for the flattery.”

“No no, it wasn’t flattery... If anything, you’re closer to my ideal type of woman,” Masato said shyly.

After all, both Miharu and Satsuki are both too familiar to me.

Their image as his guardians was too strong—he couldn’t see them in any other way.

Lilianna blinked before staring in amazement. “Well, I suppose I’m very happy and honored to hear that...”

“Ah, that wasn’t an attempt at flirting, yeah? Of course, I’d love to marry a woman as wonderful as you someday in the future, though,” Masato added in a hurry. He was talking to an older woman—a princess, no less—who he hadn’t known for long, so his tone was stiffer than normal, but he was still his usual innocent self.

“Hehe. I’m sure you will grow into a wonderful young gentleman in a few years, but if I’m still unmarried by then, I’d be considered a royal spinster. If you don’t mind marrying a mature-aged woman, then I shall happily accept your offer,” Lilianna said with an amused giggle. It felt like she had gained a fun little brother, causing her to joke around with him lightly.

“H-Huh?! D-Don’t make fun of me!” Masato yelled, blushing furiously.

“Oh? Wasn’t it you who made fun of me first?”

“No... Well, I suppose. But I didn’t mean it like that! Anyways, we’re keeping everyone waiting, so let’s hurry back.”

“Of course,” Lilianna nodded, looking only slightly reluctant. The thought of the person waiting ahead of her made her want to extend their carefree conversation a little longer...

But she couldn’t do that. Not long after they left Rio and the others, they arrived at a location not too far away.

“Yo, Bro. Aki. Thanks for waiting,” Masato said to the silently standing Takahisa and uncomfortable-looking Aki. They were surrounded by Lilianna’s knights: Hilda, Kiara, and Alice.

“...”

Neither Takahisa nor Aki said anything. While Aki looked pale and uneasy, Takahisa tried to maintain a poker face over his clearly bad mood. After the incident, Masato had gotten into a huge fight with him, making him even more sullen than before.

But Masato saw through him completely.

“You were watching, weren’t you? How was it, seeing Miharu for the first time in a few days?” he asked Takahisa and Aki. Indeed—from their current position, it was possible to see the area where they had been exchanging farewells. Takahisa had been facing the other way when Masato and Lilianna walked over, but there was no way he hadn’t been watching earlier.

“...” Takahisa’s sullen face became even more obvious.

“What? I’m here with you just as you wanted, dear brother. Shouldn’t you look a little happier?”

“...”

“Or are you saying there’s no point in Aki and me being here without Miharu?” Masato asked provocatively, not bothering to mince his words.

“Tch...” Takahisa glared at Masato sharply, but nevertheless held his silence.

“If you were watching, you should know by now. Haruto is the one who’ll stand beside Miharu, not you. Miharu won’t be happy unless she’s with Haruto. You need to accept it already—that you’re not worthy of her.”

“...” It was as though his little brother had just told him he had lost. And it was the truth—Miharu had certainly seemed happier being beside Rio. That led to an even greater sense of defeat that made him feel helpless and desperate, but he couldn’t say anything right now.

“After calling Haruto a criminal over and over again, you were the one who ended up committing a crime. Honestly, I can’t even laugh about it anymore...” Masato trailed off, looking grim.

...He’s still a criminal, too. A murderer. And yet, and yet...

Just what was different between himself and Haruto? Takahisa looked down and clenched his fists.

“I’ll tell you as many times as you need to hear it: I’m not staying with you out of pity. I’m coming along to make sure you two don’t tread down this foolish path any further. I’m not forgiving either of you until you apologize to both Miharu and Haruto,” Masato said with a huff and walked off.

“Now, please come this way, Sir Takahisa, Lady Aki,” Lilianna said to the two of them, before following Masato. Takahisa watched them leave and glanced over at the area where they had been exchanging farewells just moments ago. Although there was no one left there—

...Are you saying that I was wrong?

He had caught a glimpse of Miharu smiling happily beside Haruto, which had made his face twist with frustration. Aki watched Takahisa’s expression from beside him with a sad look.

◇　◇　◇

One week had passed since Takahisa, Aki, and Masato had departed for the Centostella Kingdom. During the week, they saw Liselotte off as she returned to Amande to deal with her work at the Ricca Guild, visited Liselotte’s parents to greet them, and formally reported to Francois about their plans to continue traveling. Time had passed in the blink of an eye.

“Aww... First Masato and the others leave, and now Haruto and Miharu are leaving. I’m so lonely! When will we get to meet up again? I wanted to eat Haruto’s cooking, too... Liselotte’s busy, so she left early, as well...”

It was finally the day when Rio and Miharu were due to leave the castle. The three of them—including Satsuki—were seated around the dining table in the living room eating breakfast in the morning when Satsuki had spoken up with dramatic sorrow. Rather than being sulky, it seemed like she was pleading to see them again soon.

“I’ll try to bring Miharu back to the castle regularly. If there’s a chance, we’ll sneak you out of the castle at night to come to the stone house—you should have said so earlier.”

“I can’t do that. You promised both Liselotte and me at the banquet, so it wouldn’t be fair to her, right? Anyways, it’d be more fun to eat together,” Satsuki said, smiling cutely.

“I understand. If I have the chance to see Liselotte again, I shall inform her then. Feel free to pass on the message if you manage to see Liselotte first, too,” Rio said with a smile.

“Yay. I’ll be looking forward to it, then. The meals at the castle are delicious, but they’re all rather oily and heavy on the seasoning. A lot of it tastes greasy, so I had them adjust it to a lighter taste, but I’ve really wanted to eat rice, miso soup, and pickled foods,” Satsuki emphasized with clenched fists.

“I agree. I could eat a Japanese meal everyday while living in that house with Haruto, but after two weeks at the castle I’ve started to miss it a lot too,” Miharu agreed with a giggle.

“Right? That’s why both of you should come back soon. I’ll be waiting! Maybe Aki and Masato will also start missing Japanese meals and come back,” Satsuki said with a laugh.

Rio and Miharu exchanged looks before nodding softly. “Perhaps.”

“...And so, I’ll be waiting for you two to return. Masato left in such a cold way, and I don’t like emotional farewells, either. If I chat with you two for too long before you leave, I’ll end up crying in front of the people in the castle, so I’m going to say this now,” Satsuki said a little sadly, staring at Rio and Miharu. She took a deep breath to calm down. Then—

“Take care, you two.” She smiled from the bottom of her heart as she saw them off.

◇　◇　◇

After breakfast, before Rio and Miharu were due to leave the castle, they met with King Francois with Satsuki in tow.

“Will you really be leaving the capital on foot?” Francois’ eyes widened when he heard the transport method Rio had chosen. As Haruto Amakawa, honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom, he was an upper-class noble on par with a count. It would normally be unthinkable for someone like that to walk out of the city with no guards.

However, inferior guards would only pose a burden in Rio’s case...

“Yes—this is what we’re used to. If the worst happens, I can run while carrying Miharu, which would be faster than a carriage.”

“Bwahaha. I see—fine, then. You don’t fit standards in a good way, after all,” Francois agreed with a smile. “Where will you be heading next?”

“I’ve made a promise with a close friend, so for the time being I’ll be leaving the area under Your Majesty’s control and heading for a city to the west. I haven’t decided on anything beyond that, however...”

Rio informed him of his general plans, stating that his plans were still rather vague. That being said, his answer wasn’t necessarily a lie. With Miharu’s situation settled for the time being, he wanted to do something to help Celia’s problems next, but it was up to her if she wanted him to do something about it so soon after they reunited.

He had yet to tell Celia that her former fiancé, Charles Arbor, had attended the banquet, so he needed to inform her of the Beltrum Kingdom news he had obtained.

“The west, hm? With the collar tab I have given you, every area of this kingdom will be accommodating to you. Friendly foreign nations should treat you as nobility. Though it may be a little strange to call you a noble of our kingdom when you are not bound by any duties... At any rate, do come to the castle regularly. Lady Satsuki and Charlotte will both be happy to see you,” Francois said with a laugh.

“It would be an honor. Miharu would also enjoy that, so I promise to visit regularly.” Rio lowered his head respectfully.

“...Good. Now, I shouldn’t keep you any longer. Charlotte, see them to the gate with Lady Satsuki.” Francois nodded.

“I understand, Father. Please, come this way.” Charlotte immediately stood up, facing Rio, Miharu, and Satsuki seated across from her. The three of them stood up and bid their farewells to Francois before following Charlotte out of the room.

After that, the four of them walked along the corridors of the castle and went outside to the gardens. Before long, they arrived at the gate.

“See you later, then, Miharu. Haruto.” Satsuki spoke to them as though she was seeing off her family while they stepped out for a moment. She didn’t like emotional farewells, which was why she kept her words short and sweet. As she had informed them in advance, she didn’t have much to say.

“Yes. We’ll be back soon,” Miharu answered, smiling a little sadly.

“Let’s meet up again soon,” Rio said after Miharu.

Satsuki ducked her head a little and nodded, then turned to look at Charlotte beside her. “Yup... Do you have something to say too, Char?”

“Let’s see. Both of you—take care. And one more thing, Sir Haruto,” Charlotte said, addressing Rio.

“Yes, what is it?” Rio tilted his head and asked.

“You heard what Father said earlier, yes? That coming to the castle would make Lady Satsuki and me happy.”

“Yes...” He had certainly heard that, but he couldn’t tell what Charlotte intended with her words, so he only nodded vaguely.

“Then, would it not make you happy, Sir Haruto?” Charlotte puffed her cheeks up slightly and questioned Rio in a cute tone.

Rio mustered an awkward smile. “Of course—nothing would make me happier than to see the two of you.”

“Oh my, is that true?” Charlotte’s face sparkled with happiness.

“Yes,” Rio nodded with a faint smile.

“In that case, how about going on a date with me the next time you visit? It’ll have to be inside the castle, though,” Charlotte said casually.

“...Huh?” Even Rio couldn’t help but be surprised by that, his honest confusion slipping from his lips. Satsuki and Miharu were both wide-eyed with shock.

“H-Hey, hey. Didn’t you say you admired Haruto like an older brother? Is it okay for you to say things like that as a princess?” Satsuki asked in a fluster.

“It isn’t that okay, but it’s just us here. None of you will go prattling about it, yes?”

Because she trusted them. It was as though Charlotte was saying that with a truly pleased face. Indeed, there was no one else in the vicinity. There was a gatekeeper by the gate, but they were far enough to be out of earshot.

“Of course we won’t... But even so... Don’t you think going on a date without someone you consider your older brother is a little too much?” Satsuki’s voice was oddly high-pitched, her face slightly panicked.

“Hehe. It’s true that I considered him to be an older brother, but it turns out I was mistaken.” Charlotte tapped her index finger against her mouth, staring at Rio with a coquettish smile. “It seems I’ve started to harbor a liking to Sir Haruto personally.”

Chapter 4: Celia’s Decision

Meanwhile, after leaving the castle and the capital, Rio and Miharu walked down the main road until they reached a completely unpopulated area and slipped away.

“You can come out now, Aishia,” Rio called out. She appeared shortly after.

“Okay.”

“You’ve been stuck in your spirit form for a while now—you must have been bored.”

“Thank you for everything while we were in the capital, Ai-chan,” Rio and Miharu both said to Aishia immediately. The hardest worker while they were in the capital had been Aishia. She acted as the messenger between them and the stone house, and worked hard in the shadows during the kidnapping incident with Takahisa.

They hadn’t told Satsuki that Aishia was a spirit, so she couldn’t materialize inside the castle. Thus, it had been a while since the three of them had come face-to-face with each other.

“It’s okay. Being inside Haruto is comfortable,” Aishia said in her usual quiet and toneless voice.

“I see...” Rio grinned a little shyly. He didn’t know what it felt like to stay inside a contract partner as a spirit form, but being told he was comfortable made him feel strangely embarrassed.

“Well, there’s no point in staying here. Shall we head home?”

“Yup.”

Thus, they decided to move from here by air. Or were about to do so, when—

“Ah, before that. I wanted to talk to Ai-chan about something, is that okay? I’ll be done soon,” Miharu said.

“...Yes, of course,” Rio tactfully agreed and gave the two of them some distance. Then, Aishia cocked her head at Miharu.

“What is it, Miharu?” she asked.

“Erm, I wanted to thank you, Ai-chan,” Miharu said a little shyly.

“For what?”

“For Haruto, and Haru-kun. You told me before we came to the capital, right? That if I want to stay with him, I can’t run away.”

“Yup, I did.”

But why did that need a thank-you? Aishia seemed to be asking that as she tilted her head.

“The reason my introverted self didn’t run away is thanks to you, Ai-chan. That’s why I’m here now. I wanted to thank you for that, so—thank you, Ai-chan.” Miharu smiled gently and hugged Aishia.

“...Yup.” Aishia nodded with a soft smile on her face, returning the hug.

“I might need your help again in the future, but if you’re ever troubled by anything, you can come and talk to me about it too. Especially if it’s about Haruto. There’s no need to hold back around me.”

“Okay.”

The two of them exchanged their feelings in a quiet but firm way.

“Shall we go, then? We shouldn’t keep Haruto waiting any more.”

“Yup.”

They broke free from their embrace and returned to Rio. They departed for the stone house without any questions from him.

After that, they spotted the stone house hidden amongst rocks within a matter of moments and descended before it. For the record, Rio had been the one to carry Miharu, who couldn’t fly yet.

“Here you go.” Rio gently set Miharu on the ground.

“T-Thanks.” Miharu’s cheeks turned red as she nodded shyly. She had already gotten used to Rio carrying her, so she wasn’t as conscious of it anymore, but for some reason she was now showing a naive reaction.

“Miharu, your face is red.”

Aishia pointed out, tilting her head.

“R-Really? I don’t think so.”

Miharu feigned ignorance in a panic. But her honesty showed on her face. She was fair-skinned to begin with, so the blush was clear enough for Rio to notice, too. He had an idea why, as well.

Normally he would write it off as being too full of himself, but he had accidentally heard the conversation between Miharu and Takahisa during the kidnapping incident.

I think I like both. The Haru-kun before he was reincarnated, and the current Haruto. I fell in love with both of them.

And so, even Rio, who was often called a blockhead, could tell when someone liked him after such an incident occurred.

“...”

However, just because he knew he was liked didn’t mean he would dig his own grave by acting out of the usual. It was at this time that the door to the stone house opened.

“Welcome back, Onii-chan, Miharu, Aishia!”

The one who leaped out was Latifa. Celia, Sara, Orphia, and Alma followed after her. With Aishia in her material form, Sara, Orphia, and Alma had noticed their approach through their contracted spirits. On top of that, they used the barriers surrounding the stone house to confirm their return and came outside.

“We’re back, everyone.” Miharu smiled brightly to gloss over the fact her fact was still flushed.

“Yes, welcome back...” Celia and the others replied, but they seemed to sense something strange about Miharu’s bright behavior—or perhaps they noticed her red face or Rio’s slightly awkward expression. They stared at them with questioning gazes.

“W-What’s wrong, everyone?” Miharu asked in a high-pitched voice.

“N-No, nothing...”

The one who answered was Sara, but everyone was staring at Miharu together. Her reaction was extremely obvious, after all. Without missing a beat, Miharu’s eyes darted about.

“Professor, there’s something I’d like to speak with you about right away. Do you have time?” Rio said to Celia with a strained smile, partly in order to rescue Miharu from her predicament.

◇　◇　◇

Rio entered the house and invited Celia to his bedroom. He sat in a chair facing her and got to the point. “I wanted to talk to you about the matter of visiting your family home. I don’t have any plans at the moment, so we can go anytime... That’s the first thing.”

“Oh... Is there something else?” Celia nodded, listening to Rio with a serious expression.

“I don’t know how important it is, but I figured you should know that Princess Christina attended along with Charles Arbor. As you can imagine, they gave Duke Huguenot’s faction the cold shoulder, and there was no sign of any possible reconciliation,” Rio explained, bringing up the name of Celia’s former fiancé.

Her face fell. “I see...”

“And there’s one more thing regarding Princess Christina...”

“Princess Christina?”

“I had a chance to speak with her before she left for a brief moment. She whispered in my ear as she was about to depart, so that Charles Arbor and the other nobles wouldn’t hear. She thanked me for saving Princess Flora during the attack on Amande.”

“...Really?” Celia’s eyes widened in surprise.

“She attended as an ambassador, so she had a certain level of freedom to move about, but her actions were probably being monitored. She was cold to Princess Flora whenever the other nobles were around.”

“...But that was all an act, right? That’s why she thanked you without anyone else hearing.”

“That’s probably the case. She used to worry for Princess Flora a lot back in the Academy, too. And the first time I met you was when Princess Christina marched into the slums in search of Princess Flora, no?” Rio said, recalling the things Christina had done in the past.

Celia looked a little apologetic. “...Yes, that’s right. I was forced to go along with her and scolded by His Majesty for it. In fact, you weren’t a very favorable existence to Princess Christina.”

“No... Well, I knew people hated me, but it didn’t really bother me. She was harmless compared to the other noble children, and never tried to harass me directly at the Academy. She argued with me the first time we met in the slums, but avoided me afterwards.” Rio smiled wryly, certain that Christina had gone out of her way to avoid him.

“...Hey, is it really okay?” Celia asked timidly.

“Is what really okay?”

“It wouldn’t be strange for you to have complicated feelings—or you know, hatred—towards the Beltrum Kingdom. But my family and I are nobles from Beltrum, and I can’t fully throw aside my position. I have to move for the sake of the kingdom, meaning you have no choice but to assist for my sake...” Celia said with a look of deep contemplation.

Rio sighed. “...Isn’t it a bit too late for that? I told you once during the banquet already, in this very room. If there’s anything I can do for you, just say the word. I’ll make it happen. That’s why I carried you away from that wedding. So please don’t forget your feelings from when you snuck away from the ceremony, Professor,” he said gently.

“...But the situation’s different to the last time we spoke. You’re an honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom now, right? I don’t want you to cross dangerous bridges for my sake and put yourself in a precarious situation... Miharu only just reunited with her hero friend. What if she can’t meet her any more? And isn’t Miharu your childhood friend from your world before you were reborn?”

“Yes, that’s true...”

“In that case, you should take good care of Miharu. Your childhood in this world was spent in the Royal Academy in a situation like that... And before the Academy, you lived a painful life in the slums, so you don’t have anyone to call your childhood friend here. Isn’t that right?” It seemed like Celia had realized who Miharu was. It was almost as though she was telling Rio to treasure Miharu over herself.

“If we’re talking about childhood friends, then I have one in this world, too,” Rio said tiredly.

“...Huh? Wait, really?” Celia blinked. That was news to her.

“She’s right in front of me. My important childhood friend in this world is you, Professor.”

“...W-What... D-Don’t tease me like that!” Completely caught off-guard, Celia stuttered speechlessly before blushing and yelling.

“I’m not teasing you. You were with me between the ages of seven and twelve, you know? If it’s a matter of years spent together in this world, then I’ve known you the longest,” Rio said with confidence.

“B-But... I’m your professor. To call me a c-childhood friend is...” It made her happy. But did she have a right to such a thing?

“Didn’t I tell you in the past that I consider you my friend, Professor? Have you forgotten?” Rio chuckled.

“I’m... your friend?” Celia asked uneasily.

“Yes. Are you not? Of course, I consider you my teacher, too. Wait, didn’t we have this conversation back at the Academy, too?” Rio tilted his head at the strange sense of deja-vu. He was sure they had a similar conversation in Celia’s old research laboratory at the Academy, but he couldn’t remember it clearly. But despite that—

“At any rate, it’s true that Miharu is important to me. But you’re important, too, Professor Celia. If Amakawa Haruto’s childhood friend is Miharu, then Rio’s childhood friend is Celia Claire. That’s what I believe, at least,” Rio said with resolution.

“Uhh...” Celia was rendered speechless and reddened by the fact that Rio had spoken so frankly to her face. She was fairly certain it was the first time she was called by her full name.

“You’re an important person to me, Professor. That’s why I couldn’t overlook your marriage to Charles Arbor when I knew it would only make you unhappy. That’s why I extended my hand to you. You took it. Nothing has changed about the situation since then. There’s no need for you to hold back.” Rio held his right hand out to Celia.

“W-What...?” Celia looked down at the hand Rio offered nervously.

“We can head to your family home whenever you want. We can even leave as soon as today or tomorrow, if you’d like. You just have to take my hand.”

With his hand still extended, Rio encouraged Celia to make a decision. A single teardrop rolled down Celia’s cheek.

“D-Doing this for someone like me... Just don’t blame me if it doesn’t go well.”

She started crying as she gently grabbed Rio’s hand.

◇　◇　◇

After their conversation, Rio left his bedroom and headed to the living room. Celia shut herself in Rio’s room, stating that she didn’t want to be seen crying.

Upon reaching the living room, Rio witnessed the sight of Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma surrounding Miharu, hounding her for answers. Aishia sat alone a short distance away, yawning sleepily.

“S-So did you ask him? Or rather, did... Did you manage to c-c-confess to him?” Sara asked Miharu nervously.

“I-It wasn’t a confession! I didn’t say it to him directly, so it d-didn’t count.” Miharu waved her hands in denial.

“But it’s true that you conveyed your feelings to him, right?”

“Yeah. At this rate, Miharu’s going to be one step ahead...”

Alma and Orphia also appeared to be slightly panicked.

“Hmph! So you did love Onii-chan, after all, Miharu!” Latifa pouted unhappily.

“...Umm,” Rio said to the room awkwardly.

“Wait, Rio?!”

They had been so absorbed in their conversation that no one noticed that Rio had been in the living room for a while now. Everyone other than Aishia flinched.

“...Err, what were you all talking about?” He had pretty much figured out what they were discussing, but it was so awkward, he decided to feign ignorance.

“I-It’s nothing!” Miharu yelled with a flushed face.

“Anyways, what happened with Celia?” Sara cleared her throat and asked.

“We were talking about visiting her family home. I’m thinking of leaving as early as tomorrow to head to the Beltrum Kingdom to the west, so I wanted to inform everyone of that. We should have enough hands with Aishia coming along, so if the rest of you want to remain here, it’s an option...”

Sara and the others exchanged glances before enthusiastically offering to go together.

“Of course we’ll come along!”

Chapter 6: Escape

“S... Sweet Celia?! Why are you here?!” Roland Claire shouted at the sight of his daughter in the hidden basement of his home. Her being here was truly right out of the blue.

S-Sweet Celia? For a moment, Rio doubted his ears.

“Father, I asked you to stop calling me that...” Celia said to Roland with a strained smile. He spread his arms and hugged her.

“Have you been well? I was delighted to find your letter and hear that you were safe after you were taken away from the wedding, but I worried so much.”

“I’m very sorry for doing such a thing without informing you...”

“No, you did the right thing. If I had to give that piece of shit your hand in marriage, I’d rather you remained unmarried for the rest of your life!” Roland stressed. It seemed like he doted on his daughter quite a bit. Roland was slender and on the slightly smaller side, but his dignity and spirit made him seem like a youthful middle-aged man. However, he appeared rather sloppy at the moment.

“Umm, Father. We’re standing front of Princess Christina, so please watch what you do and say,” Celia said with a strained expression.

“O-Oh, that’s right. Hmm. I had information to pass on to the princess, too, but...” Roland looked conflicted. He surely had many things he wanted to ask Celia, such as where she went after she left the castle, and what she was doing here now...

“If you’re really short on time, please speak with Professor Celia first. It’s your long-awaited reunion, after all,” Christina said, understanding how Roland must be feeling.

After all his hesitation, Roland made a decision. “...No, I shall make my report to you first, Your Highness.”

The situation must be dire, Christina realized, causing her to stiffen.

“I understand. It doesn’t seem like it’ll be good news, but please let me hear it.”

“Yes. The truth is, the capital has sent additional search teams, and they’re being led by Charles Arbor. A distrustful and despicable man who uses everything within his means. He deemed the mansion to be the most suspicious location and has called for all the city’s carpenters to gather tomorrow and dismantle my house in search of hidden rooms. He’s even prepared a seizure warrant from His Majesty to make sure I cannot refuse. There’s absolutely no time left,” Roland explained as he watched Celia with a conflicted expression. Celia looked pained to hear that Charles was so close by.

Christina looked at Rio imploringly. “...Sir Amakawa. Is it possible to leave tonight?”

“It is. There’s no other time than tonight to leave, it seems,” Rio answered immediately.

“...Your Highness, who is this boy?” Roland looked at Rio and tilted his head.

“He’s the newly-appointed honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom, Sir Haruto Amakawa.”

“Honorary knight? At such a young age? But what is a noble of Galarc doing here...?”

“Sir Amakawa is the one who brought Professor Celia to this underground room,” Christina explained.

“W-What? How did you get around all the security guards outside...? No, wait. If you’re the one who brought Celia here, then are you...?” Roland looked at Rio in surprise.

“I am also the one who took Lady Celia from her wedding,” Rio stated.

“O-Oh my... H-Hmm.” Roland stared closely at Rio’s face and hummed.

“Father, like I previously wrote in the letter I left here, I was the one who decided to flee from that wedding. Haruto simply granted me that wish.” Celia emphasized that it was her own intention to run away from the wedding ceremony, shifting all of the responsibility away from Rio.

“...I know that. So you’re the one who saved Celia. Sir Haruto Amakawa, please allow me to thank you.” Roland placed his right hand over his chest and bowed his head at Rio.

“No, I was the one who pushed her into questioning whether she wanted to be married in such a way. I apologize for causing you any degree of concern.” Rio bowed his head back in apology.

“I thought my heart would stop after she was kidnapped, but it resulted in her escape from marrying Charles, I suppose. I’ll let you off with a single blow from the fire magic Ignium,” Roland stated with a refreshing smile.

“Father! Please don’t misunderstand. I was the one who decided to leave the castle. The responsibility is on me, not Haruto. If you wish to blame anyone, blame me. I’m the one at fault!” Celia pouted in objection.

“No, you can never be wrong!” Roland denied immediately.

“Then you’re not wrong, either, right?” Celia confirmed.

“But of course!” Roland nodded, beaming with his entire face.

◇　◇　◇

At the same time, Christina and Celia’s group had made it through the wheat fields and were running down the road through the forest.

“Hah... Hah... How much further... do we have to run?” Kouta panted.

“Keep going! Don’t waste a single second of the time Sir Amakawa bought us!” Vanessa yelled from where she ran in the lead.

“Eek...” Kouta’s upperclassman, Rei, wailed in a pitiable voice.

Celia and Christina were in a similar state, having already passed the limits of their stamina long ago. However, they shared Vanessa’s feelings and continued running desperately.

Ten more seconds passed like that, when everything in Vanessa’s field of view suddenly went dark.

“...What?” She looked up towards the sky, questioning.

“MROOOR!”

A pitch-black minotaur came falling out of the sky with a rumbling impact. On top of that—

“ROOOAR!”

Crash. There was another one behind them.

“Wha...”

The party had come to a stop before they realized it, staring upwards in a daze.

“What... are those...?” Rei stiffened.

“That... was at the academy during the outdoor drill that one time...” Christina recalled the time they encountered a minotaur at the academy’s outdoor drill and paled.

“I-It’s a minotaur! W-Why is it here?!” Celia, who had actually witnessed one before, yelled.

“MROO!”

“BRREH HEH!”

The minotaurs laughed heartily with their warped faces.

“T-There’s more... coming from the forest...”

Vanessa was about to suggest escaping into the forest when a group of orcs noisily made their way out from between the trees. They were completely surrounded on all sides.

With none of them able to move, they stood there as still as can be. Then, the minotaur behind Celia extended its left hand, reaching for Christina. However—

“MROOR?!”

The black giant was unable to grab onto her body, as it was blown away forcefully from the side, crashing into the orcs by the forest loudly. Meanwhile, the spot where the head of the minotaur had just been was replaced by Alma.

“A-Alma?!” Celia muttered her name in shock. Alma must have swung her mace into the minotaur’s head from behind, as she landed on the ground in a stance to catch her momentum.

“Guh... Grrguh...” The beaten-up minotaur tried to stand up weakly, but failed.

“We’ll cover you! Please fall back!”

Another voice that Celia recognized rang out. A silver flash passed by her—it was the silver werewolf, Sara. Sara approached the minotaur struggling to get up and cut off its head without giving it a chance to react.

“Grr...”

The defeated minotaur disappeared into ashes. However, the area was still swarmed with orcs, some which had been crushed just moments ago. Sara immediately stepped back and distanced herself from the remaining orcs.

She was replaced by a rain of countless light arrows, piercing through the bodies of the orcs gathered. The one who attacked was the high elf standing ten or so meters away from the group—Orphia—holding a bow.

“W-Why... are you guys...?” Celia asked the newly-arrived, dumbfounded. The three of them had the physical traits of their species altered into human ears through magic artifacts.

“We came to assist. Was it unnecessary?” Sara asked a little awkwardly.

“N-No, you saved us...”

“It’s not over yet. Let’s clean up the remaining big guy and the orcs in the forest,” Alma said, holding the mace in her hand ready.

“Celia, please fall back to where Orphia is with the others.” Sara glared at the minotaur standing before them.

Christina was bewildered by the rapidly-changing situation. She turned to Celia in confusion. “P-Professor Celia, who are these girls...?”

“These three are Haruto’s friends. At any rate, everyone! Come this way!” Celia gave a short answer and pulled Christina’s arm, giving an order to Rei and Kouta standing beside them on the way. Meanwhile, Vanessa was holding her sword up against the orcs.

“O-Okay...” Despite how she had stiffened up, Christina retreated at Celia’s guidance.

“MROOOR!” The remaining minotaur roared to intimidate the escaping party and leaped into the air.

“Did you think we would falter at something like that?” Alma looked up at the minotaur in disgust.

“We’ve been underestimated, it seems. Orphia, force it back!” Sara glared at the minotaur sharply as she directed Orphia behind her.

“Yup!” With a nod, Orphia quickly fired arrows of light from her bow. The thick beams of light flew straight through the air and towards the body of the soaring minotaur.

“Gragh?!”

The minotaur promptly used the stone greatsword in its hand to block the arrows, but was knocked back by the impact.

“Wha...” Christina watched the scene with wide eyes. The attack just now had enough power to be a higher class of intermediate magic, yet it was impossible to fire that in less than a second with the knowledge within Strahl region.

Could that bow be an ancient artifact? She looked at the beautiful bow in Orphia’s hand. However, while she pondered that, Alma and Sara abruptly disappeared.

“Alma, slam it into the ground! I’ll finish it off!”

“You don’t need to tell me twice.”

Sara started dashing in the direction the minotaur was blown in while Alma leaped high into the air with her mace braced. The two of them had physical abilities that far surpassed those of humans.

“MROR?!” Alma, with her petite size, slammed her mace into the minotaur’s giant body, making it rapidly change directions and crash into the ground.

Sara caught up to the minotaur in the brief moment its body was rebounding back into the air and cleanly sliced off its head. The next time the pitch black body hit the ground, it dispersed into ash.

This left the orcs lurking in the forest.

“Grr, guh...”

The violent orcs seemed to be cowering after watching the minotaurs get overwhelmed so easily.

“Gragh?!”

Orphia released numerous arrows of light at once, eliminating the orcs in a matter of moments. Each arrow was pinpoint-accurate with no sign of missing their targets. As a result, the orcs were completely wiped out in a flash.

“...There are no more presences.”

“It seems like all the monsters have been eliminated.”

Sara and Alma swept their eyes over the forest around them as they approached Celia and the others.

“Good work, you two,” Orphia giggled.

“?!”

Suddenly, the three of them assumed their battle stances towards the forest. The next moment, a black flash of light weaved its way through the trees, aiming their way—but it wasn’t targeted at Sara, Orphia, Alma, nor Celia.

“Huh?”

The target was Christina.

By the time they realized this, the rapidly-moving black light was right before their eyes and they were unable to move, rooted to the spot. It was the perfect surprise attack with no trace of the assailant—nobody present was able to react.

It was too late to evade. Just as they thought that, a dark shadow cut before Christina. It was, of course—

“...H-Haruto!”

Celia’s eyes shined the moment she recognized him. Rio held his sword in his hand to take on the black light from head-on—when, the next moment, he swung his sword and completely erased the light.

Clap, clap, clap. Just then, someone started applauding from within the forest. The sound of the clapping gradually grew louder until a person soon appeared.

“Ah, how splendid. I was thinking of assisting when you all encountered so many unforeseen enemies, but they were taken care of so quickly.”

Reiss clapped as he walked out of the forest, commending Rio and the others.

“...You.” Rio narrowed his eyes. It was a face he recognized—the person who had taken Lucius away after he cornered him during the monster attack on Amande.

“I’m honored that you remember me. My name is Reiss, a member of the Heavenly Lions.” Reiss introduced himself not as an ambassador of the Proxia Empire, but as a mercenary.

“After Amande, I’m assuming these monsters were your doing as well?” Rio asked.

“Why, I would never. How could one even control such monsters? Didn’t I just say I was thinking of assisting?” Reiss shrugged, exaggerating his feigned ignorance.

“Then what was that final attack you aimed at Princess Christina?”

“Oh my, are you accusing me?”

“Who else could it be?”

“There could be another enemy hiding, no?” Reiss answered with a grin.

“The enemy is you.” Rio glared at Reiss with suspicion. The same went for everyone else present.

“No, no, I have no intention of fighting here. I was just visiting Cleia by chance when I noticed you, so I thought I’d say hello. It seemed like you were caught up in your own business, so I couldn’t find the right timing to do so,” Reiss said in a smooth voice. He suddenly remembered something and added in a delighted tone, “Oh, that’s right. The one you have a connection with is doing quite well, too.”

“...Where is Lucius?” Rio asked coldly.

Celia and the others around them listened silently to the conversation, unable to keep up with the situation, but they noticed the air around Rio was more tense than usual and gulped.

“He holds a fairly large grudge towards you, so you’ll be reunited sooner or later. From the avenger to the avengee, if you will... Human karma is a truly difficult concept. Wouldn’t you agree?”

Reiss smiled provocatively, but Rio’s expression did falter.

“Isn’t that right, Rio?” Reiss said with a grin.

“Guh...”

Celia, Sara, Orphia, and Alma swallowed their breath on Rio’s behalf. How did he know Rio’s name, they wondered. But on the other hand—

...Rio? Wh...?!

Christina was wide-eyed as she stared at the back of the person who just saved her. Instantly, all her suspicions about the person named Haruto Amakawa were answered, everything connecting together like a puzzle. She inadvertently gulped. It wasn’t as though she accepted it as the absolute truth. Perhaps, just perhaps... Such feelings of denial also rose within her. But, despite that...

“...”

Rio lifted his sword and watched Reiss sharply, ready to slice into him at a moment’s notice.

“Oh dear. I will take my leave now, so please put away that dangerous-looking sword.” Reiss held both his hands out before him, dramatically stating his refusal to fight.

“...”

Rio continued glaring at Reiss, expression unchanged.

“Of course, I can keep you company if you insist, but if you dawdle around here the pursuers may catch up, no? You seem to have multiple burdensome people in tow... it would be a shame if they were targeted first in battle. Would you be able to protect them all if it came down to it? You don’t even know the limits of my power yet, hmm?”

Do you still want to try, anyway? Reiss’ smile implied.

“...Disappear before I change my mind.”

“My my, how scary. Then, if you would excuse me.”

At that, Reiss retreated back into the forest. Rio watched his back with a grim expression.

Interlude: The Pursuers

While Rio and Celia were walking around the city of Cleia during the day, Count Claire’s estate was welcoming some honored guests.

A dozen or so men walked down the hallway. In the lead was the man formerly engaged to Celia, her ex-fiance Charles Arbor. Immediately behind him was Beltrum Kingdom’s strongest swordsman, the King’s Sword Alfred Emarle, and the hero Shigekura Rui. Further behind them were Charles’ knight subordinates.

“Has Princess Christina still yet to be found?!” Charles yelled in irritation as he threw open the doors of the room acting as the headquarters of the search party set up in the mansion.

“S-Sir Charles! I see you have made the long journey from the capital. I apologize for not coming to meet you!” The knight in charge of the search party had been seated at the desk glaring at documents, but he leaped to his feet in a hurry to salute them.

“Forget that. Where’s Princess Christina?”

“S-Sir! The search is ongoing, but we are yet to find her!”

“You better be searching properly.”

“O-Of course, Sir!”

“And Count Claire?”

“He insists that he doesn’t know anything. We’ve placed him under house arrest to monitor him, and he hasn’t shown any suspicious movements so far. Are you sure Princess Christina came this way?”

“I am. Not only is Cleia en route from the capital to the Restoration headquarters in Rodania, Count Claire is the only noble on the side of the crown who would assist the princess. He’s the only noble of that faction who departed from the capital at the same time as her disappearance, too,” Charles stated in irritation.

“However, if that were the case, she may have already departed from the city...”

“That’s why we have personnel divided to all the nearby cities and roads. And, even if she has left the city already, we need to obtain evidence of Count Claire’s collaboration.”

“There’s still the possibility that Count Claire really wasn’t involved...”

“...Are you a fool?” Charles asked, briskly closing in on the search party captain.

“The First Princess vanished from the capital. Who will take responsibility for that? Hmm? Will it be you? Are you the mastermind behind it?” he whispered in his ear.

“...N-No, Sir.” The search party captain shook his head fearfully.

“Then gather all the carpenters in the city here tomorrow,” Charles suddenly said.

“...Huh?” The captain was stunned, unable to understand the reason why carpenters needed to be summoned.

“They’ll be used to threaten the count. Just summon them here. I’ll speak to Count Claire myself,” Charles said with a twisted grin.

“Y-Yes, Sir! Understood!”

“Good reply. Now, rejoice.” Charles turned around and introduced Rui and Alfred standing behind him. “Some reliable figures will be cooperating with the search party. This is our kingdom’s hero, Sir Rui Shigekura, and the King’s Sword, Alfred. Though it pains me to cause such trouble for Sir Rui like this...” He pressed his hand against his forehead, expressing his grief for making Rui assist them.

“My friend and upperclassman disappeared, as well, so I’m more than happy to help out. I look forward to working with you.” Rui pasted a cheerful smile on his face as he greeted the search party captain.

“I-It’s an honor, Sir!” The knight captain saluted nervously.

“And so, Sir Rui, you will be moving in a pair with Alfred for the search party. You may also use my other personnel if needed.”

“Sure, leave it to me.” Rui nodded easily.

“Alfred, protect Sir Rui with your life, got it? Your little sister is complicit in this. You must take your own share of responsibility.” Charles narrowed his eyes at Alfred threateningly.

“...I am aware.” Alfred nodded quietly. Just then, a knock sounded on the door of the search party headquarters.

“Who is it? Enter,” Charles turned to the door and said.

One of the guard soldiers entered the room, saluting them once before opening his mouth to pass on a message.

“Sir Charles, someone identifying themselves as your old friend Jean Bernard has arrived. What would you like to do?”

“...Jean Bernard? W-What? Why... N-No, lead him to a room immediately. Treat him with respect. I shall head there immediately.” At Charles’ order, the knight saluted once more before departing quickly.

“Who is that? I haven’t heard that name before,” Alfred immediately inquired.

“It was mentioned already. He’s my friend. One I have known for a long time.”

“Is this the time to be meeting with old friends? How did he know you were here when we only just arrived ourselves?”

“He must have been in this city by coincidence and witnessed us entering the estate. I cannot keep him waiting, so I will go now. Sir Rui, please excuse me,” Charles said, immediately turning on his heel and leaving the room.

◇　◇　◇

Charles immediately moved to the drawing room to wait for Jean Bernard’s arrival. Less than a minute later, his arrival was announced.

“Jean Bernard is here.”

“Let him through. Don’t let anyone else inside,” Charles ordered.

Reiss soon entered the room. “Why, if it isn’t Sir Charles. We just met at the banquet the other day, but how have you been faring since then?” He gave a friendly smile as he bowed politely.

“...Should I be referring to you as Lord Bernard right now, Lord Reiss? How did you know I was in this city?” Charles asked, wanting to know the details of why Reiss was here.

“Oh, no—I was simply tracking the movements of someone I’m curious about and ended up in this city. I noticed a rather heavy atmosphere, then found you in the midst of it, so I thought I’d at least say hello. I named myself Jean Bernard, as the Proxia Empire ambassador being here would probably cause a bit of a stir and arouse needless suspicions,” Reiss said, smiling with profound meaning.

“Is that so? What a coincidence it was, then.” Charles frowned regrettably. “I would love to give you a proper welcome, but, as you can see, we’re all a little busy right now.”

“Keep it between you and me; if you’re facing some kind of trouble, I can offer my support. Did something happen?” Reiss asked with a worried expression.

“The truth is... Well, we suspect a felon has concealed themselves in this city, so we’re investigating that.” Charles was about to explain the situation in detail, but stopped with just a vague description instead. No matter how much he trusted the other man, he hesitated to tell a foreigner that the princess escaped her supervision in the castle.

“Oh my, that sounds dangerous, indeed. If you are moving directly, then that felon must have committed a grave sin.”

“Yes, well. I wouldn’t describe them as villainous, but they are cunning,” Charles said, thinking of Christina.

“I see... Well, I shouldn’t interfere with the matter of another kingdom too much. It wouldn’t do for me to hinder you from your duties any longer, so I shall excuse myself now.” Reiss seemed to read the room and offered.

“My apologies. I must meet with Count Claire now. If you are staying inside the city, I can have a guest room prepared for you...”

“No, I have already secured lodgings, so there’s no need to concern yourself,” Reiss said, standing up.

“I see... I’m truly regretful that I couldn’t offer better hospitality. Let us speak more leisurely the next time we meet.”

“Yes, gladly. Now if you would excuse me.” Reiss nodded with an empty smile and left the room.